askstudent.com 2015-04-26

# Privacy Policy - AskStudent | AskStudent

This privacy statement covers the site [http://www.askstudent.com](http://www.askstudent.com/ "College Student"). AskStudent takes your privacy very seriously and we created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. By visiting AskStudent.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Notice.

For some services , we direct you to other merchants/advertisers through links on our site who may collect and use your personal information. In those cases the third-party service provider or merchant’s privacy policy will govern how your information is handled. We encourage you to ask questions and to be very cautious before you disclose your personal information to others.

 **This Privacy Policy will explain the following regarding use of our site:  
**

**What information does AskStudent.com collect from you?**

Current Site  
AskStudent.com is the sole owner of information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to any outside parties. Certain Non-personal Information may be collected automatically as part of your use of this Site, as well as from your transactions with us and our affiliates or non affiliated third parties. This Non-personal Information is used to improve the overall Site operations, functionality, appearance and ad customization. Non-personal Information may include your IP address, web browser type, domain name and the time or date upon which you visited the Site.

Potential Future Upgrades  
We plan to introduce a personalized section for our visitors. Once this personalization becomes operational , we plan to collect information from our customers to process orders and better serve you with pertinent information such as customized ads etc. We would also require you to submit a user name and password of your choice for your future access to your account information. To safeguard that your user name and password remain confidential, DO NOT share this information with anyone. Also, we plan to roll out a newsletter for our customers. If you elect to receive our newsletter or special promotions, your contact information will be used for the delivery of these items.

 **What is your cookie policy?**

We customize certain Web page content based upon your browser type and other information provided by our cookie. However we also provide links to other third party websites. The third party website may set cookies and it is governed by their privacy policy.

 **Does AskStudent.com Share the Information It Receives?**

We do not share your information to any third party. All information that we collect are kept securely and confidentially with us. They are used as per policy mentioned in this statement.

 **How does AskStudent.com uses the information that we collect?**

Personal Information is used by AskStudent.com for the purpose for which it was submitted. For example, if you submit your email address and other information required to subscribe to our newsletter, we will use that Personal Information to send you our newsletter. Please see below for your Choice/Opt Out options.  
If you to use our “Tell A Friend” referral service to inform a friend about our Site or a deal, we will use your email to inform your friend. We will send the friend a one-time email inviting them to visit the Site, all email addresses entered in “Tell A Friend” are not stored.

 **What security precautions are in place to protect against the loss, misuse, or alteration of your information?**

AskStudent.com makes every reasonable effort to preserve user privacy. However we reserve the right to disclose Personal Information when required or permitted by law and we have a good-faith belief that such action is necessary to comply with an appropriate law enforcement investigation, current judicial proceeding, a court order or legal process served on us.

 **What About Third-Party Advertisers and Links to Other Websites?**

Linking. This Statement applies only to [http://www.askstudent.com](http://www.askstudent.com/ "AskStudent"). Please be aware that our site may contain links to other sites on the Internet that are owned and operated by third parties. The information practices of those websites linking from or to our site are not covered by this Policy. These other sites may send their own cookies to users, collect data, or solicit personal information. Additionally, other companies or ad servers, which place advertising on our site may collect information about you through the use of cookies when you view or click on their advertising. We cannot control this collection of information. You should contact advertisers directly if you have any questions about their use of the information that they collect.

Google and the DoubleClick DART cookie:

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on AskStudent.  
Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to AskStudent’s users based on their visit to AskStudent and other sites on the Internet.  
Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html "Google DART cookie opt out").

Google Analytics Tracking code for Display Advertising:

  * AskStudent uses Google Analytics features based on Display Advertising (e.g., Remarketing, Google Display Network Impression Reporting, the DoubleClick Campaign Manager integration, or Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting).
  * Using the [Ads Settings](https://www.google.com/settings/ads), you can opt-out of Google Analytics for Display Advertising and customize Google Display Network ads.
  * We also encourage you to visit Google Analytics’ [currently available opt-outs](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout/) for the web.

Kontera

We use third-party companies to serve ads and collect non-personally identifiable information ( _e.g.,_ the pages you visit, and which links you click, which ads you see and click on, and the categories of search terms you enter) when you visit our web site. These companies may use the information outlined above (which does not include your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. These companies often use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) (link to the NAI universal user opt-out).

 **Are Children Allowed to Use AskStudent.com?**

You must be at least 18 years old to have our permission to use this site. Our policy is that we do not knowingly collect, use or disclose Personally Identifiable Information about visitors under 13 years of age. If you are the parent or guardian of a child under 18 years of age and have concerns, please [contact us.](http://www.askstudent.com/contact-us/)

 **Privacy Policy changes**

If AskStudent.com makes changes to any terms or conditions of the Privacy Policy, the changes will be posted in this document so that you will always know what information we gather, how we might use that information and to whom we will disclose it. We may change, modify, add or remove portions of this Policy at any time, and any changes will become effective immediately upon being posted unless we tell you otherwise.

 **Need more Help?**  
You can find the answers to most questions in the [AskStudent.com FAQ page ](http://www.askstudent.com/faq/ "Ask Student's FAQ page")

Last updated: Sep 29, 2013
